I think I used my head a
little bit too much last time.
My shoulders are real sore.
They feel so heavy.
Thank you
very
much.
Thank you.
Uki araru kine nai hokori no kizuna.
Naoko yurishimete!
today.
Oh, I don't know.
What do you think?
Well, white is always nice, but I think
something colorful can
be kind of fun, too.
I'll let you decide.
Okay, let's see.
I think
the white one is pretty, but I really
like the lovely design on this one.
I wonder if
Jojo and Caesar have
passed their final exams.
I have a bad feeling.
I'm beginning to worry.
So today, we're going to go with
the pretty white. Susie Q. Yes?
Please send Suzi and Jojo to
my room as soon as they arrive.
Yes, of course, Signora.
I know I said I like the white
blouse, but the other one is nice too.
So which is better?
Which do I choose? White.
But then again, this is really nice too.
Ay, what do I do?
The colorful one will
do nicely, thank you.
Excellent choice!
I'll just leave this
here for you, alright?
I'll come back later and
clean up the broken glass.
Be careful, okay?
I will, thank you.
Hey, Susie Q.
What are you screaming for?
Be quiet, you stupid idiot.
Who are you?
There's a stranger on the island!
Hey, wait!
You think I'm a stranger?
It's me, you dummy.
Joseph Joestar.
Huh?
Hmm.
Jojo?
No way!
When I saw you before, you
were always wearing a mask.
Wow, what a surprise!
What?
Are you telling me you've never
seen my face in all this time?
So, what do you think? Am I handsome?
Hmm.
Weird lips.
Well, they may be weird, but if we were
ever to fall madly in love with each other,
you'd be welcome to kiss
them all you'd like.
Yeah, in your dreams.
What's the matter?
Uh, nothing at all. Really.
Oh, yeah.
Signora Lisa Lisa wants you to
go up to her room right away.
But she is taking a bath, so you
should probably wait half an hour.
Got it.
I was planning to go anyway.
I've got to tell her that
they know all about the stone.
Huh?
Oh, no, you're not talking
about her stone, are you?
Uh, don't worry about it.
You really don't want to get
involved in all this stuff.
Believe me. Okay.
Jojo, wait a minute.
What's up?
You're actually pretty hot, you know.
That's odd.
My shoulders feel like they've
suddenly started to loosen up.
The news I have to report
is really important.
But Lisa Lisa is taking a bath.
So I'm going to have to
wait for half an hour.
Until she's done.
If I was told to wait then
waiting is what I'll do now.
Where to spend half an hour I think the
Best place is here by Lisa Lisa's door.
Would it really be all that
wrong if I took a peek?
through the keyhole to check things out.
Nice!
Susie Q?
Wait a minute, what's she doing in there?
I didn't even see her go into the room.
Well, that was really fast.
I thought she was still out on the docks.
What the hell?
The doorknob is completely
covered in some kind of goo.
Susie Q, tell me, have Jojo
and Caesar made it back yet?
Susie Q.
Are you all right, Susie Q?
What's going on?
What did you do with the red stone?
Who are you?
Tell me what you did with the red stone.
No, this is bad.
It seems something has
taken over Susie Q's body.
You, you have reduced me to nothing
but a brain with no body of my own.
But nevertheless, I challenge
you to one last fight.
I put the stone on the boat
that just left the dock.
I am here to stop you from
chasing it and getting it back.
I will not allow you to follow
that poster boat, no matter what.
The woman I am inside of is
still mostly alive, you see.
There is only one way
for you to destroy me
completely and that is
to take her life as well
Can you do that?
Are you capable of that?
ACDC! Jojo!
You won't stop coming at us will you?
You don't give up!
Jojo!
Oh Caesar, well, it's about damn time.
You are...
So you managed to survive
your bout with ACDC?
You're a lucky one.
That's for...
Jojo!
What the hell were you doing
in here with our coach?
Hey, cool it, you meathead.
It's not like that, okay?
Just take a look at Susie Q.
All right, then.
What's going on?
It's ACDC.
Damn him.
He somehow figured out a
way to make his brain and
blood vessels invade her
body and take control of her.
Save me, Caesar.
Please help me.
Everyone picks on me all the time.
But you'll never pick
on me, Caesar, will you?
Don't fall for a word of it.
Susie Q is not doing the talking.
ACDC is manipulating her. That's right.
She managed to take the stone
and put it on a postal boat.
Leave this thing to Jojo
and me and find that boat!
Get the stone back!
If the red stone reaches Venice
and is transferred onto a train,
we'll lose track of it and have no
way to know where it will end up!
You're not going anywhere, dickheads!
If you want to stop that boat or leave
it all, you'll have to kill me first!
A male voice!
I see what's going on.
His blood vessels must be
controlling her from the inside.
Yeah, come on. Bring it.
Use your hormone and kill me.
It should be a relatively easy task for
you to destroy me in my current state.
But then again,
you must know that this
girl's heart isn't nearly
strong enough to endure a
hormone shock and survive it.
Are you willing to snuff out this
girl's life in order to defeat me?
If you are, then hurry up and do it!
Quit standing there and wasting
time, you stupid dickheads!
Hey!
I'm not soft-hearted, ACDC.
All I have to do is end
the life of one young girl,
and I'll be able to save
the entire world from you.
I would consider it a small
but necessary sacrifice.
Wait a minute!
Are you serious, Jojo?
Time to tear you into
little tiny pieces, ACDC!
No, you can't! JoJo!
I'm not kidding here!
I'm really gonna do it!
Damn it all!
I just can't hit her!
The bastard!
I thought he'd pop out of her
when I started to make my move,
but it didn't even faze him!
Enough of your bluffing!
You can never kill this girl
no matter how hard you tried!
Hehehehe!
By now I'm sure the stone has
already arrived on the main island.
You're too late!
And now...
The bastard!
What is he doing to Suzy Q now? Stop!
Don't do this, ACDC!
And now, just to make things interesting?
I will make this girl's body
explode and cover you all in blood!
that burns as hot as flowing lava!
Look out!
His blood is boiling hot!
Suzy Q's body, it's
beginning to fall apart!
If this keeps up, it won't be
just Suzy Q who'll be in trouble.
It'll be all of us as well.
So, we have no choice.
Jojo, you need to use your
hormone on her right now.
Come on, no!
I don't want to do this.
Please don't make me.
I'm still having to deal with
all the horrible nightmares
I get about the time I chopped
Von Stroheim's leg off.
A different plan.
We need a different plan right now.
All right.
I'll do it then.
No, hold on a minute.
Coach, let me do it.
Wait, don't do anything.
I thought of something.
Caesar, do you remember Helcline Pillar?
We can give that a shot.
It's do or die, so let's go for it.
You and me, two types of Harmon
at the same time. Two types?
Yeah, I see what you're saying.
You're right, something
like that might just work.
You know what to do then.
Jojo! Caesar!
Right, I understand.
Jojo, I want you to follow my breathing.
Let's go!
JoJo creates a burst of positive
Hamon and surrounds Susie-Q with it.
Caesar creates a burst of negative
Hamon focused on her heart.
At that point, the Hamon is
both negative and positive zero.
It worked!
You forced AC-DC out!
Jojo!
Don't worry.
It's all right.
We'll just let the sun
take care of the rest.
That low-down, dirty scum!
Hiding in a girl's body like that!
He's nothing but a coward!
No, Caesar.
You don't get it.
I fought against him, so I understand.
You see, he gave all he had.
and even threw away his pride because he
felt a duty to get the
stone for his allies.
For thousands of years, he did as he pleased,
and he lived his life to its fullest.
Whether it was good or evil, I respect
his life and how he chose to live it.
Jojo!
Susie Q,
while ACDC controlled you,
you must have been at least
semi-conscious most of the time.
Now tell me, where is the stone headed?
Switzerland.
San Moritz.
A package.
An envelope with Signora
Lisa Lisa's crest.
The address is...
Switzerland?
What about cars in Wamuu?
Are they there? Hmm.
I just checked with my
contact at the station.
A cargo train for Switzerland
left not ten minutes ago.
That's it.
The stone has to be
somewhere on that train.
They've got a big head start,
but we've got to somehow figure
out a way to get ourselves to St.
Moritz before that train arrives.
We have to do everything we can to keep the
stone from falling into the wrong hands.
We might even have to do a
little bit of dirty work.
A few laws might be broken as well.
Some of us may even end up in body bags.
Don't worry, I won't.
I wasn't ready before, but now
there's no way I'm gonna lose.
I'll eradicate every one of them.
Let's go.
Right, we're out of here.
Hey, Suzy Q! Look over here!
It's goodbye for now, Suzy Q.
I don't know when or how, but
I'll be back in Venice one day.
I promise!
Really?
Yeah.
Peel those ugly wounds on your
face before I get back, will ya?
Later!
Jojo, be careful!
Make sure you come back
in one piece, okay?
Don't get pushy!
You may be an old lady before
I get back, but I will return.
Oh, yeah?
You're a stupid jerk!
I'll be back a lot sooner than you think.
Screams
Hey, it drives a damned car, really? Huh?
What's happened to your arms, man?
Huh?
Something's wrong with the wheel, man.
I can't get it to move.
Hmm.
ACDC hasn't reported back.
He last said that he had learned
the stone was somewhere in Venice.
I wonder if something has happened to him.
Hey, Jojo. Jojo.
Jojo, wake up!
Jojo, we've caught up with the train.
They're going through their
customs check at the moment.
That works in our favor.
We're less than an hour from San Moritz,
which leaves us enough time to get ready.
It's good we caught up.
Come on, Jojo. Look sharp.
Listen, I'm just saving up my strength
for the big battle, that's all.
Get off my case!
Let's hurry up and get there
so we can retrieve that stone.
Then we're going to need some sort
of plan for the fight with Wamu.
We'll wait for that until we cross.
What the hell?
Knock it off!
If you want to go on, just
quit honking and pass us.
German soldiers What the hell are they
doing in a car on the Swiss-Italian border?
Well, well, you're looking rather spry.
My, you have grown so much, Joestar. Huh?
What did you say, mister?
What was that about?
Get back here!
Who the hell are you?
What's going on?
I don't know any German soldiers.
Hey, look at the train!
So many soldiers.
Hey, Major, we found the package!
The crest.
Look, they've got the package.
Yeah, and we all know what's inside.
The Red Stone of Asia!
I don't understand.
Why do the Germans want it?
We have decided to take this stone as a
specimen for our scientific
research program.
For the past three weeks,
we have been watching your every move
while you were operating in Venice.
We began the surveillance
when we lost our team in Rome.
We saw your training, we saw ACDC, and
we knew you were chasing the stone.
Now, our base is set up at
a lodge up ahead. Follow us.
We want to ask a few questions
about the stone and about cars.
Why not work together, eh?
After all, we are not
complete strangers, Jojo.
Hey!
What are you blabbering about?
Don't think you know anything
about me, you bastard!
If the Germans are here, that means...
What do we do, Koch?
We have to follow them.
At least we know Crazy doesn't
have the Redstone, either.
At that time, the German army
was marching across Europe,
taking country after country.
They wanted to ensure their rule across
the continent would last indefinitely.
The power of the Mask and
Redstone would solve their problem
perfectly by giving them everything
they would need to prevail.
The Germans were planning
to use the ultimate
power of immortality to conquer the world.
I'll read the heat inside.
The fireplace is lit.
Four lights on the wall, two on
the ceiling, two on the desk, no.
Three.
Four humans standing by the wall.
Their heights are 178, 174,
181, and 178 centimeters.
One human is by the fireplace,
183 centimeters tall.
There are five humans, all male.
One, two, that's four and five.
So you must be cars.
You're fast.
In just a few hours you heard
about your friend's defeat?
Learned that we had obtained the stone!
Found our location and have come for it.
Very impressive!
And then this brutal,
perfectly calculated assault.
Not one of my men made even the
slightest sound before they died.
I was sure there were only
five men in this room?
Now tell me, why can't
I sense your body heat?
Hey, rifle heads! What's...
what's a guy gotta do to
get a little food in here?
Cars!
Huh?
This man's mechanical.
Wait a minute.
You're von Stroheim!
I'll take you out and out.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the chill and drum really ring.
I'll spend the day your way.
Cold in morning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
One mile over, we'll be there.
And we'll see you.
Ten and two summers, we'll
be there laughing too.
Twenty-four, we'll fall by the real sea.
I'll be there with you.
We shot the tack now!
The building on top of that hill is
the address That was pretty mean.
German science is the finest in the world!
No machine can stop me.